<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>evangelism on Equipped Youth Manual</title>
    <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/categories/evangelism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in evangelism on Equipped Youth Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/categories/evangelism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Timothy 1:15</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/1-timothy-1-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/1-timothy-1-15/</guid>
      <description>Here is a trustworthy saying that deserves full acceptance: Christ Jesus came into the world to save sinners—of whom I am the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you a good person?</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/videos/are-you-a-good-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/videos/are-you-a-good-person/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Graham</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/testimonies/billy-graham/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/testimonies/billy-graham/</guid>
      <description>One day in May 1934, 15-year-old Billy Graham came home from school and set out to pitch hay to the mules with one of the hired hands at his family’s farm on the outskirts of Charlotte, North Carolina. The two heard singing from behind the barn, and the hired man wondered aloud what was happening.
“I guess they’re some fanatics that have talked Daddy into using the place,” Billy replied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ephesians 2:10</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/ephesians-2-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/ephesians-2-10/</guid>
      <description>For we are God’s handiwork, created in Christ Jesus to do good works, which God prepared in advance for us to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can I tell others about Jesus?</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/questions/how-can-i-tell-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/questions/how-can-i-tell-others/</guid>
      <description>Pray and ask God to give you the right words to say and to show you the best time to say them. Then explain the simple good news of salvation. Here are some tips.
First, people need to understand that they are sinners. Many people think that all they have to do to get into heaven is live a good life and try to be nice to others. The problem is that every person on earth has sinned (done wrong things that God has said not to do), and sinners can never be allowed into heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John 3:16</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/john-3-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/bible_verses/john-3-16/</guid>
      <description>For God so loved the world that he gave his one and only Son, that whoever believes in him shall not perish but have eternal life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is there suffering?</title>
      <link>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/questions/why-is-there-suffering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://realiveyouthdev.azurewebsites.net/questions/why-is-there-suffering/</guid>
      <description>Study the soil for a moment. It naturally produces weeds. No one plants them; no one waters them. They even stubbornly push through cracks of a dry sidewalk. Millions of useless weeds sprout like there’s no tomorrow, strangling our crops and ruining our lawns. Pull them out by the roots, and there will be more tomorrow. They are nothing but a curse!
Consider how much of the earth is uninhabitable. There are millions of square miles of barren deserts in Africa and other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>